( Church bells peal )
( Guide ) Watch your step . Watch your step , please .
Hispanic Tours , this way , please . Follow my hand .
- No , no , no . - The usual postcards ! ( Laughs )
- Photos , photos . - No , thanks . I 'll take my own .
Follow me .
This way . This way , please !
( All chatter )
All right .
Here we are , ladies and gentlemen .
Keeping close , please .
Come along , move in close , please .
Here we have , ladies and gentlemen ,
a unique example of Medieval Christian art .
This representation of the devil carrying off the dead ,
goes far beyond the formalized art of its day .
Look closely .
The face of Satan expresses a quality ,
which reflects the very soul of pleasure in evil .
The devil seems a presence so strong and overpowering ,
that this painting has led to a local superstition .
The people of this region believe that it is only the power of the devil himself ,
which has kept this fresco from ruin .
- Listen , I 'll be right back , OK ? - Lisa , where are you going ?
- Wait for me there , all right ? - Yeah , well , hurry back .
( Guide ) ... balanced between the figures of the living and of the dead .
( ♪ Distant music box plays )
( ♪ Music box plays )
( Man ) Hm , the eyes , Maestro . ( Shopkeeper ) Sí , señor ?
( Man ) I would add a few wrinkles and age them a bit more , hm ?
- His attire , Maestro . - Hm ?
A bit severe , isn 't it ?
Well , I think this black here would be better , you know ,
because then you could use it on all occasions -
for funerals , weddings , whenever you like .
- Hm , you have a point . - Oh , I 'll trim the mustache a little .
( clears throat ) Excuse me , but how much are you asking for this ?
It 's not for sale . It belongs to the gentleman here .
Oh .
( Man ) Up we go ! ( Chuckles )
( Man ) Do you think black is too severe , Miss ?
( ♪ Music box continues to pay )
( Man ) Strange , how strange . You 'd think the girl had seen the devil !
Excuse me , sir , could you tell me ...
No , wait !
Sir , the main square ...
Señora !
Excuse me , señora , but I 'm Lost . Can you tell me where the main square is ?
( Asks for directions in simple Spanish )
( Cackling Laughter )
( Man approaches , speaks )
brain and mouth agape .
You 're a dummy , is what you are . ( Chuckles )
Ah , is she the Lady we met in the shop ?
- Hello , Miss . - Excuse me , I ... I ... I 'm Lost .
Can you ... Can you tell me where the main square is ?
- ( Gasps ) - Come back here ! ( Chuckles )
Excuse me . The square , what square ?
Well , the one ...
Well , the one where the painting is ,
the , er , fresco of the devil carrying away the dead .
Ah ! That way .
Good day , Miss .
Good day .
( Mumbles )
Darling !
- Elena . - ( Whimpers softy )
Why do you Look at me like that ?
- No ... - You knew that I 'd come back to you ,
- that someday we 'd find each other again . - No , don 't ...
You must have known that I would have come back .
- No ! No ! - No , Elena !
- Let me go ! No ! - ( Screams )
( clattering )
Help !
He ... help !
( Car approaches )
Hey !
( Man ) What is it now ? ( Driver ) I don 't know , sir .
( Man ) You 're a chauffeur ...
( Driver ) Yes , sir . I 'm not a mechanical engineer .
( Woman ) Must you use that tone ? ( Man ) please !
- please , open ! please ! - ( Man ) What 's the matter ?
Excuse me , but I 'm a tourist , and I 've Lost my way .
( Man ) All right ...
- ( Man ) George ! - Yes ?
( Man ) We 'll give this young Lady a lift .
( George ) We will if we can get started .
( Man ) May I know what 's wrong with the car ?
It 's the upper hose . It 's Losing water , sir . It should be repaired .
Let 's go on .
( Engine rattles )
( Man ) Why are you slowing down ? ( George ) It 's not me , it 's the car , sir .
( Man ) Listen , George , do you have to stop right here in the middle of nowhere ?
It 's not up to me , sir .
If it 's boiling over , we can 't go much further , not without burning out the motor .
( Woman ) You and your foreign cars .
What do we do now ? Wait for parts to come in from the factory ?
( Man ) Stop that , will you ?
How do you open these ? George ?
- ( George ) Madam . - Next time , listen to me .
( Woman ) Thank you , George . ( George ) Madam .
( Woman ) How Long will it take ? ( George ) If we had a hose , a few minutes .
( Woman ) Can 't you fix it ? ( George ) I could try .
( Woman ) please , George .
( Door creaks )
( Man ) Oh , er , good evening . I , er ...
I 'm very sorry to bother you but we 've had some trouble with the car .
The water hose is Leaking and we 'll need a mechanic .
( Woman ) Leandro ! ( Man ) I realise it 's Late ,
but if we could use your phone and get in touch with a garage ...
( Woman ) Leandro !
I 'm sorry , there is no telephone here .
We have so little use for it , you see .
- ( Woman ) Send them away ! - Yes , my Lady , certainty !
( Man ) Is there a hotel nearby ?
( Leandro ) No , not in the immediate vicinity .
Oh , there are a few roadside inns ,
but their accommodations would hardy meet with your approval .
( Man ) I see .
( Gasps )
( Woman shouts in distance )
( Leandro ) Coming , my Lady !
( Woman ) Oh , this is awful . ( Man ) Yes , it 's a dreadful night .
Please stay .
Don 't go away .
( Man ) Where could we find one of these roadside inns ?
No , no , no , please , don 't go away .
My mother 's not used to visitors . We live atone .
But please , please come in .
( Woman ) Maximilian , what 's keeping you ?
Excuse me , I 'll ... only be a moment .
Mother .
Tell them to go , Maximilian , dear , listen to me .
W ... we 're always so atone .
It 'll only be for one night . Mother , please .
She ...
They 've no place to go .
Only for one night .
- Very well , if you wish . - Oh , thank you , Mother .
Max ... not in here . Show them to the cottage .
( Frogs croak )
It 's just ahead .
A few more strides ...
- Thank goodness for that ! - Sophia !
Well , we could at Least tell George where we 're going .
Would you care for a Lollipop ?
You know , the villa 's a bit run-down , but I 'm sure the cottage will be suitable .
Besides , even the Countess would prefer it . Miss ...
- Erm , you and I earlier this evening , yes ? - I ...
I mean , you were lost and asked for directions .
- You do remember , don 't you ? - No .
I do most of the shopping for the Countess and I 'm often in town .
And very little escapes me , if you know what I mean .
( Woman ) Well , are we supposed to stand here all night ?
- ( Man ) Listen there , where is this place ? - Excuse me .
Come , please . Come this way .
( Leandro hums )
( Woman ) Oh , it 's so slippery .
( Leandro ) There 's a bit of moss here ...
and there ... and everywhere . ( Laughs )
( Woman ) What 's the matter with him ? ( Leandro ) Come , Miss !
( Engine rattles )
This way .
Here we go .
Straight on .
That 's it . Excellent !
Excellent !
( Creaking )
- ( Gasps ) - ( Clock chimes )
( clock chimes )
- Now , where 's your husband ? - Guess !
Oh !
Taking his bath .
The first thing he did was to go look for a tub . ( Chuckles )
No need to worry .
He knows about us . He 's not blind .
It 's just that he doesn 't care .
Don 't look like that .
Hm ?
( Man whispers ) I love you .
( Gasps )
( Rattllng )
( Screams )
What 's the matter ? What 's wrong ?
What frightened you so ?
That 's only Leandro .
( Leandro ) Messy ... dummy ! ( Woman ) No , no , no , it ...
( Woman ) It wasn 't Leandro , it was ... ( Maximllian ) Oh , he was carrying a dummy .
- Oh , it was awful ! - The villa 's full of them . They 're harmless .
Don 't cry .
Don 't !
This is such a gloomy house . We 're so alone .
You can 't imagine how ... how happy I am now that you 're back .
Back ?
This is the last rose of the season .
It lingered on and waited for you .
If only you would stay ! Don 't go away .
( Woman ) I ... I don 't even know you .
( Maximllian ) Everything 's so different with you here .
I feel alive and happy .
( Woman ) But ... ( Maximllian ) Don 't say no. please !
( Woman ) Maximllian !
Is that you there ?
Yes , Mother !
Excuse me , I have to go now . I 'll see you at dinner .
( Leandro hums )
Good evening , Mr Rabbit , or is it Mr Hare ?
Would you care for a radish ? No ? They 're very good . ( Hums )
( Max ) I 'm very pleased you decided to accept our invitation . Thank you .
( Sophia ) Thank you . ( Man ) Yes , thank you .
( Man ) Our intrusion wasn 't very timely .
( Max ) Oh , no , no , no . You 're most welcome .
Our mother 's not used to visitors . She was a bit frightened , that 's all .
It was all so unexpected . You understand .
- Yes , of course . - ( Max ) So thrilling .
( Sophia ) Thrllllng ?
( Max ) You must be tired . Was it a long trip ?
That depends on the starting point , I wouldn 't know how to answer that .
- ( Max ) Oh ? - I never plan things that far ahead .
I certainly envy you . A new horizon emerges for you each day .
My world , instead , is the very configuration of this villa . I ...
( Max ) Mother ! Oh , excuse me .
I 'm so glad you came down . Thank you , Mother .
Good evening .
Leandro , I would llke to be introduced to our guests .
I 'm Francis Lehar .
My wife Sophia and I wish to thank you for your kind assistance .
( Leandro ) That will suffice , thank you .
Your Ladyship , may I present Mr and Mrs Francis Lehar .
And may I also present Miss , er ... Miss , er ...
Lisa . Lisa Reiner .
Miss Lisa Reiner .
- please be seated . - Thank you , Your Ladyship .
Our guest Mr Lehar was telling us just before you arrived , Mother ,
of his journeys . He has the world in the palm of his hand , it would seem .
- ( Francis chuckles ) - Where 's the other person ?
Other person ? You must mean the chauffeur .
- He 's outside . - No , not the chauffeur , dear .
I mean the fifth person who came here this evening .
Mother , believe me ...
Maximllian , dear ,
you haven 't forgotten him , have you ?
It 's so easy to imagine a mysterious visitor in this house .
Yes , thank you .
- Rare ! Very rare ! - Mm-hmm !
The entire setting is so right for a tall tale of gloom and perdition .
( Chuckles nervously )
We could make one up as we go along .
We have the right ingredients .
The dark night .
This house .
It 's all so ... so spooky .
Don 't you find , Your Ladyship ?
I prefer ghosts to vampires , though .
They 're so much more human . They have a tradition to live up to .
Somehow they manage to keep all the horror in without spilling any blood .
( Clattering )
( Footsteps )
( Floorboards creak )
( Footsteps continue )
( Banging )
( Max ) Mother , please !
Mother , listen to me , please . You 're tired .
( Woman ) What 's wrong , Maximllian ? ( Max ) Nothing . Don 't worry .
- I told you he 'd be back . - Mother ...
I ...
I was not introduced to the fifth guest , Maximllian .
- ( Smashing ) - ( Sophia gasps )
( Chuckles )
please ! Excuse me , but I ...
I 'll only be a moment . Do continue , please .
I have to ...
Leandro , the cake .
- It 's with chocolate sprinkles . - Thank you .
Leandro , perhaps our guests would llke some cake also . It 's quite good .
Please continue . I ... I 'll be right back .
Excuse me .
( Walling )
I brought you some cake .
It 's your favourite .
With chocolate sprinkles .
Did you know he was back ?
You mustn 't see him .
You must send him away .
I wlll not let him come between us again .
He 's caused enough anguish .
He 'll never enter this room !
You 've nothing to say ?
- You 're not asleep . - ( Moaning )
You can pretend if you like .
But you 'll never leave this room !
( Walling )
Do you hear me ? Never ! Never .
- That should do it . - ( Leandro ) You 'll be leaving at once ?
Uh-huh .
( Leandro ) Quite adept with these mechanical toys , aren 't you ?
So-so .
Thanks for the ... Oh !
You 're over there . Thanks for the tape .
Could you tell the others to get ready ? I 'll be through here in a minute .
- Of course . - Thanks .
That didn 't take much , did it ?
( George ) No , just a lot of tape .
Most things aren 't that easy to mend .
How could you come back ?
After what you 've done to us !
Mother ...
Mother was certain that you 'd return .
She was certain .
But I never thought you 'd have the courage .
Why did you have to come back now ?
Just when I found happiness .
I won 't let you destroy everything .
You can 't take her away again !
Where are you ?
How can I stop you ... when I can 't even see you ?
Where are you , you coward ?
Show yourself !
Oh , finally ! This is so nerve-wracking .
Lisa , we 're leaving as soon as the car is ready
but we 'd be glad to take you if ...
Oh , erm ... I don 't think our young lady will be going with you .
Master Maximllian has asked her to stay .
Come . Come closer , girl .
The eyes , Leandro . What colour are the eyes ?
Changeable , my lady .
But by candlelight ...
blue .
She 's blind . My God !
And the hair , Leandro ? Tell me of it .
Tell me of the hair .
Light , my lady , and gently flowing .
Golden like a field of wheat ?
No , my lady , brighter still .
And haloing an equally beautiful countenance .
Oh , she 's a very lovely creature , my lady .
You wouldn 't listen when I told you to stay away .
Now it 's too late .
Frank , this is ridiculous .
( Sighs )
I 'm going out of my mind , Frank .
These people are all crazy .
What 's happened to George ? What 's going on ?
Where 's George gone , dear ? To fix the car !
Calm down , will you ? Calm down !
All right . I 'll go out and take a look .
And you calm down !
( Engine revving )
( Car klaxon )
Oh , it 's about time !
( ♪ Music box plays )
Hm ?
I find that invariably , Miss Lisa ...
there 's a very simple explanation for almost everything .
Don 't you agree ?
( Car horn )
( ♪ Romantic music plays )
It 's cold ...
- ... you 're trembling , darling . - Oh , Carlos .
When I saw you , I ...
I had to come back and help you in some way .
To give you life and happiness .
Oh , Carlos , my love !
I love you , Carlos !
( Moans )
Carlos , I love you .
Carlos , oh ...
Don 't leave me , please .
The thought of losing you fills me with such sadness .
I don 't dare think of it .
Oh , my love , you 're back !
I 've waited so long for you .
No !
George ?
George !
Where are you ?
George ?
George !
Oh , where did he go ? George !
- ( Francis ) What 's the matter ? - Oh , Geor ...
- Where have you been ? Did you find him ? - Obviously not .
Your concern for our chauffeur is almost touching .
Where are you going ?
If this is your way of being a man , Frank ...
- ... I 'm very unimpressed . - You slut .
Let go of me !
( Sophia screams )
( Sophia weeps )
Why ?
( Sobbing )
( Continues to sob )
Oh ...
( Sobs )
We must go to notify the police .
No , we don 't want anyone coming now .
It 's all so horrible .
To think Mother predicted it ...
We mustn 't call them . They 'll pry into our lives , and ...
And I 'll be guilty .
It 's not always wise to stir up the past .
We all have some unforgivable secret .
Sarah , let us leave well enough alone .
Careful !
Your mother imagined there being someone else in the house .
If we haven 't seen them , there must be a reason , don 't you think ?
If you would take my humble advice , Mr Lehar ,
it will be best to leave at once .
Oh , yes . I understand .
Would you say my chauffeur discovered something he wasn 't supposed to ?
Who knows ?
We all have enemies , Mr Lehar .
And what better place to get rid of someone undesirable ?
Undesirable ?
Why ?
- What enemies are there in here ? - Hm .
But not to worry .
All you have to do is go and leave the corpse to us .
Now , Mr Lehar , can I trouble you for a cigarette ?
- Oh , yes . - Hm .
- Leandro ! - ( Leandro coughs )
Excuse me , sir , would you mind putting out those cigarettes ?
The smoke bothers the Contessa .
- You called , my lady ? - Where is my son ?
Is he with the girl ?
I don 't know .
Get rid of her . We must send her away .
Oh , Lisa .
What good is it to hope for the future when solitude is all that awaits you ?
What else is there to live for ?
What else matters after having felt the joy of your presence ?
- When I ... - Hm ?
When I think of my life and on what poor stuff my dreams were fed !
I feel such futility in growing old .
If you were to leave me , I 'd ...
No . No , it is I who shall never leave you .
Oh , Maximllian .
What evil spirit forces you to utter such words ?
- Have you no pride ? - No .
I have no pride when it comes to words ,
what things I do .
I only have the greatest regrets for what I have not done .
Mother , please .
Try to understand . If you knew how desperate I feel ...
We both know how it will end , Maximllian .
No , you 're wrong . You 're wrong this time , Mother .
( Contessa ) No , my son .
( Max ) It will be different . You can 't stop me , Mother .
( Contessa ) Oh , my poor child !
( Max ) I 'm no longer a child . Let me live my life .
( Contessa ) Come , Maximllian , come ...
No , don 't shout .
Be quiet ! Don 't make a sound !
Shh ! Quiet !
Quiet , my love !
You must believe me . I want to help you .
For years I 've waited for this moment , trust me .
We must flee from here .
Wait for me here . I 'll go and see what he 's doing .
Wait for me , my love .
( Leandro sings ) ♪ Should old acquaintance be ... ♪
( Clears throat , continues singing )
♪ Say it with flowers ... ♪
Hm .
( Strains )
- Sorry . - ( Bones crunch )
( Hums )
( Gasps )
Elena , what 's the matter ?
- I heard you scream . - ( Screams )
No , wait . I want to help you ! Come back !
Elena !
( Pants )
No , wait !
( Panting )
- Elena . - ( Screams )
Why did you run away from me ? I told you I want to help you .
I love you .
( Sobbing )
If you 're through mourning your lover we can leave .
Let 's go !
( Sobbing )
Come on !
Go on , get in !
Frank , I 'm not coming with you .
- I 'm staying here until George is buried . - Get in the car .
We can do without the chauffeur .
( Francis screams )
( Tyres screech )
( Woman moans )
Don 't be afraid , my love . Elena !
We 've suffered so much , but it 's over now , my love .
I 've come for you . It 's all ending .
Elena !
( Exclaims )
( Screams )
( Shrieks )
( Water drips )
( Screams ) No ! Help !
Help !
HELP !
( Sobs )
( Screams )
No ! No !
( Leandro imitates the Contessa ) Hurry , Leandro !
Yes , my lady .
( Imitates the Contessa ) The ceremony 's about to begin .
The ceremony 's about to begin .
The ceremony 's always about to begin .
Oh , hurry , Leandro . ( Chuckles )
That 's easier said than done .
Excuse me . ( Chuckles )
Look at that head .
Newly moulded this morning and already it 's split !
Must be that synthetic glue .
Mm , that 's what it is .
( Hums )
Hm .
Neither glue nor spllntered heads can stop the funeral .
The ceremony must go on . The Countess is waiting .
Waiting ... to bury the dead . ( Chuckles )
The poor Countess isn 't so wrong , really .
Wanting to get rid of him .
He 's not ... a very pleasant memory .
A man ... losing his head .
( Laughs ) That 's pretty good .
A man losing his head .
Hm . A husband .
A husband losing his head ...
over a woman ? ( Tuts )
Shame on you . But still , the Countess wants his body repaired .
She wants it put in working order for the burial .
Tradition , she says . More work , I say !
All this tradition .
I wouldn 't mind if I had any .
But what does tradition mean to a poor devil like me ?
Work and fatigue , that 's my inheritance .
They break , they snap , they pop , they crackle ,
and I 'm the one who puts their tradition back together again .
( Gargles )
Hm !
And now I 've got another puppet to make .
Lucky for me , you look just like her .
Because ... you won 't be around tomorrow , that 's for sure .
I knew you 'd be back .
Everything 's been ready . We were only waiting .
But you didn 't come back here for me , your wife .
You came back for her .
You saw her . She was in that body .
And you came back for her .
( Leandro ) Gently .
Ever so gently .
Ah !
( Hums )
Oh , blast !
The irresponsibility .
( Sniffs )
Such devilish acts .
Hm . Hmm .
Where there 's smoke , there 's fire . ( Chuckles )
Is this the face that launched so many deaths ?
A modern-day Helen ?
Cleopatra ?
Sleeping Beauty ?
And I 'm Prince Charming .
Oop ! Didn 't work .
- ( Lisa groans softly ) - Hm .
Sleeping Beauty awakens .
How do you feel ? Did you sleep well ?
( Hums )
23 .
( Leandro hums )
- It isn 't ... - That 's good . ( Hums )
But ... but it ... isn 't possible .
Oh , be careful. please don 't touch . The glue is still wet .
- Size ... six and a half . - But he can 't be ! He spoke to me !
Hm ? Well , that 's no reason to faint dead away .
It 's quite possible that he spoke to you . I mean , this is Señor Carlos .
That 's the Countess 's husband . Maximllian 's step-father .
I mean , why shouldn 't you have seen him ? He was here . ( Chuckles )
No , don 't you see ? It can 't be .
I ... I know he 's dead . I saw him in his casket in the chapel !
In the chapel ? No , no , no , no .
You saw this dummy in the coffin .
You see , it 's a dress rehearsal for the funeral ceremony .
Oh , by the way , I dropped it and it broke on the way here ,
but please don 't tell the Countess . I mean , I fixed it .
You can hardly tell , can you ? Hm ?
Then Carlos is ... is alive .
Isn 't he ?
Oh , no .
Señor Carlos ... is dead .
Hm .
( Creaking )
( Clattering )
Max ! Max !
Leandro . Leandro !
- Yes , my lady ? - I heard her running , calling for my son .
Hurry , Leandro , there is no time to lose . Tell me , does she really look ...
Oh , yes . Oh , yes , my lady .
She is Miss Elena in person .
- We must find her . - Yes , my lady .
( Sobbing )
Maximllian !
Your mother is after me .
We 'll go away ... the two of us .
I 'll help you escape . We 'll start a new life together .
My mother is jealous beyond reason .
I don 't want to spend the rest of my life in this nightmare .
No . No .
Help me . Please , help me to leave .
( Contessa ) That room . Find her , Leandro ! You must find her .
( Max ) Shh ! Quiet , don 't move .
( Contessa ) Are you searching , Leandro ?
Answer me .
We must find her before Maximllian does .
( Contessa ) Leandro !
You 're so beautiful .
I didn 't think there could ever be a girl as beautiful as you .
You 're even more beautiful than Elena .
Elena ?
Come .
- Come . - Where are we ... ?
No , I don 't want to think about her now .
She brings back so many sad memories .
I loved her deeply , yet she deceived me .
- Come , I 'll show her to you . - Maximllian , I ...
- Don 't worry . - I ...
Come , it 's all right .
Come , my love .
This is Elena .
( Screams )
- ( Lisa whimpers ) - No , don 't , Lisa !
No , Lisa . No , my love , you mustn 't do that. please !
I told you , she means nothing to me now .
Belleve me , my love . She means nothing .
I love you. only you .
Belleve me .
She could have helped me . I begged her to .
- But she wouldn 't . - ( Lisa sobs )
She wouldn 't do it .
It 's true , she wouldn 't . She wouldn 't .
- Here . - ( Muffled screams )
Forgive me , my love . My only love .
Now , we 'll always be together .
You and I.
Always .
It will be different with you .
I know it will .
It has to be different .
It has to be .
( Breathes heavily )
( Sobs )
( Laughs )
( Max laughs )
( Woman 's cackling laughter )
( Cackllng fades )
- Leave me . - ( Woman laughs )
- Leave ! - ( Woman laughs )
- I can 't with you here ! - ( Woman laughs )
- Why don 't you leave me ? - ( Woman laughs )
- Why ? - ( Woman 's laughter fades )
I hate this smell of death !
We don 't want funeral trimmings !
This is a wedding ceremony !
Do you understand ? A wedding ceremony !
What will that change ?
It 's all my fault .
- I should have stopped you . - No !
- I should never have let you meet her . - Quiet .
After what you did to Elena .
After what I did to Elena ?
- Maximllian , please . - And what about what she did to me ?
- She ran away with your husband . - Maximllian , I forbid you to talk that ...
Your husband !
Yet Carlos never knew why she didn 't join him .
I avenged myself and you at the same time .
No , it 's not as simple as you think , Maximllian .
Now they 'll come looking for all those people .
Why did you do it , my child ? Why ?
- They were going to take my Lisa away . - That would 've been better for all of us .
That stupid driver .
I had to stop them !
That girl will be the end of us . You must get rid of her .
No . No !
If we cover every trace of what happened here , there 'll still be a chance .
Otherwise they 'll take you away , and you wlll be punished , my love .
I can 't go on like this !
I can 't live like this in your shrine of death !
- It 's all around me ! - Maximllian .
I want to live .
I want to be free . I want to be with people !
- I understand , poor child . - Don 't call me that !
I 'm your mother .
No-one can understand you as I do , or protect you as I do .
Listen to me .
You will be saved only if Lisa disappears .
- Lisa . - Listen to me , my child .
Lisa . Go .
- Get out . - Don 't talk that way to your mother .
You are very cruel with me today ,
but I forgive you .
I know you don 't mean what you say . Do you , my darling ?
Say that you love me .
( Screams )
( Gasps )
Leandro !
Leandro ! Where are you ?
Leandro ! Answer me !
( Gasps )
Leandro !
( Gasps ) No ...
No ! Mother !
No , please , no !
No .
No !
Mother , please ! I ... I ...
No . No !
( Thudding )
They just never stay put .
Oh , it slipped .
( Sobs )
( Gasps )
( Squawking )
( Max ) Lisa !
Lisa !
You shall never leave me .
We 'll always be together .
Don 't go ...
Don 't go !
( Chlldren chanting ) One ... two ...
Hey , come back !
She 's a ghost . Everyone knows that .
No one 's lived there for a hundred years .
- She 's a ghost . - A ghost !
- Let 's run ! - Oh my God !
Oh my God !
Hm ...
Here you are , Mr Leandro .
It 's the best I could do . I had such a short notice .
I do hope you think it 's all right , sir .
Oh ?
I 'm afraid it 's all too late , my friend . All too late .
The airport , right away , please .
( Hissing )
( Bell rings )
( Tannoy ) ' please fasten your seat belts
'and keep your seats in an upright position .
'Kindly refrain from smoking .
'Thank you . '
( Sighs )
( Tannoy ) ' Now , this is your Captain speaking .
'We 're flying at an altitude of 25,000-30,000 feet
'at about 600-700 miles an hour .
'We expect to arrive at our destination according to schedule .
'We hope you have a pleasant trip . '
( Heart pounds )
( Heartbeat accelerates )
( Heart stops pounding )
No !
( Cries out ) No !
( Sobs )
Help ! Open up !
Someone , please ! Help !
( Sobs )
- please , Captain . - Hm ? ( Chuckles )
( ♪ Music box chimes )
( ♪ Woman sings ghostly walling melody ... ♪ )